<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<BadeventsCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Badevents>
		<Events badeventsvariation="Water is being rationed off amongst your people, those with lower social status thirst and ask for your help.">
			<Response1>Without much effort, you dip your fingers in your chalice and lightly sprinkle the sparse land below. The people are happy that rain has come their way. Some feel that this is a good sign and are gambling more </Response1>
		</Events>
		<Events badeventsvariation="An earthquake shakes the ground, people are thrown off balance and buildings wobble.">
			<Response1>With little effort, you apply force using a single finger to counter act the quake. The quake shivers in fear to your touch and dissipates instantly. Your people are as equally amazed as you are.</Response1>
		</Events>
		<Events badeventsvariation="An unexpected blizzard hits your peoples land.">
			<Response1>You perform a rite on your followers to prepare them for hibernation as the blizzard approaches. Sometime after the blizzard you nearly forgot about your followers. You quickly use the Sacred Air horn and wake up your followers to enjoy the warm Spring air.</Response1>
		</Events>
		<Events badeventsvariation="A cyclone appears and begins ripping apart your peoples houses.">
			<Response1>BLANK</Response1>
		</Events>
		<Events badeventsvariation="A volcano dormant for thousands of years rumbles close to your people. Unknown to your people, this volcano is bound to blow soon.">
			<Response1>BLANK</Response1>
		</Events>
		<Events badeventsvariation="One &quot;follower&quot; has started a movement against Your Grace as he believes the &quot;silly&quot; array of daily rituals such as the Holy Jumping Jacks are unnecessary.">
			<Response1>You appear before the nay-sayer in a dream in all your glory… then smack him across the face. The next day he hastily ended the movement.</Response1>
		</Events>
		<Events badeventsvariation="One follower claims to be a reincarnation of Your Grace and is speaking in your place.">
			<Response1>Out of jealousy for his GORGEOUS hair, you give him bad hair days for the rest of his pitiful existence. A trend is set amongst your followers for this hairstyle.</Response1>
		</Events>
		<Events badeventsvariation="An unorganized nomad tribe has stumbled upon your peoples land and has started an attack">
			<Response1>BLANK</Response1>
		</Events>
		<Events badeventsvariation="A neighboring nation has disrupted your peoples thousand year Yo-Yo trade route.">
			<Response1>You honestly could care less about your people's Yo-Yo trade route as you've recently gotten into Cubing. However, you decide to place a hastily put together vision in the trade masters head in which he slides four inflatable life savers under each leg of a camel in preparation for sea travel as an alternate route. Trade continues again but at a slower pace.</Response1>
		</Events>
	</Badevents>
</BadeventsCollection>