<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<GoodeventsCollection xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Goodevents>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="A follower wishes to throw a festival in your name but is struggling to find the funds and theme.">
			<Response1>The follower was only able to muster up enough to throw a small get together with friends and family. The follower tries to reconnect with his disappointed father who wished for his son to become a tax collector. He fails.</Response1>
			<Response2>Your followers settle on a camp fire singalong lasting all night.</Response2>
			<Response3>The follower throws a massive blowout, party large enough to be heard from the heavens. Drinks were drank and fun was had.</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="The elders of the village are debating to build a monument in your glory!">
			<Response1>After a lengthy debate your elders have produced a Sacred Stool.</Response1>
			<Response2>After hours of debate, your elders create a statue of your likeness out of twigs and thread.</Response2>
			<Response3>Your elders have decided on allocating funds and resources towards a mighty cathedral in your name where they may bask in your glory.</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="A holiday is around the corner.">
			<Response1>Everybody gathers around the ground fox in anticipation for its shadow!</Response1>
			<Response2>Everybody is wearing yellow and drinking more water than usual for that day.</Response2>
			<Response3>The patron saint of free things appears in front of your people to hand out gifts of and mushrooms.</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="Friendly nomads appear in the village. They show an interest in the culture of your people.">
			<Response1>A wandering nomad appears in town and is intrigued by the multiple statues and temples to Your Grace. He wishes to follow your light.</Response1>
			<Response2>A lost family stumble upon your peoples land. The family takes it as a sign that the first thing they see in</Response2>
			<Response3>A wandering nomad tribe finds your peoples land and is amazed by the elegant temples endowed in purple cloth and garnished with fountains to Your Grace. They all are convinced that you are a loving, caring, responsible, and sane God and wish to follow your light.</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="Someone has wondered into town, he has volunteered to become the next sacrifice.">
			<Response1>A follower who has always dreamed about being a sacrifice after attending last years sacrifice ritual wishes to present himself early.</Response1>
			<Response2>A follower who has convinced some of his friends to be a sacrifice for Your Grace wish to give themselves up early.</Response2>
			<Response3>A follower has started a cult in your name and is planning an early mass sacrifice. You giggle whilst jumping up and down in glee.</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="A harvest has occurred.">
			<Response1>Cakes have been found in the field completely spotless of dirt and manure.</Response1>
			<Response2>All pests such as mice, bunnies, and locusts spontaneously explode and are used for great fertilizer.</Response2>
			<Response3>The legendary golden mushrooms starts appearing all over the land!</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="Something has washed ashore! Your followers go to investigate.">
			<Response1>A message in a bottle appears, filled with words of encouragement.</Response1>
			<Response2>Treasure washes ashore filled with multiple gems shaped like mushrooms.</Response2>
			<Response3>A beached whale presents itself to your people by carving itself open and handing out its blubber. Even though you had nothing to do with this, your people still thank you.</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="A ship has wrecked on the shore, the crew mates are confused but also interested in your followers culture.">
			<Response1>Most of the ship wrecked crew were zealots and would rather be killed then follow your light.</Response1>
			<Response2>Convinced some who were ship wrecked and killed the rest. (?)</Response2>
			<Response3>Your people force the ship wrecked crew to convert to Your Grace.</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="Visiting dignitaries.">
			<Response1>The dignitaries appear and present gifts of gold, mirth, and perfume!</Response1>
			<Response2>The visiting dignitaries wish to listen to Your Wisdom.</Response2>
			<Response3>The visiting dignitaries bring with them a 50 foot bronze statue in your image.</Response3>
		</Events>
		<Events goodeventsvariation="Gods visiting from a different Pantheon.">
			<Response1>Steve, the god of loose change, brings lots of change to your people. Emits an aura of mild happiness.</Response1>
			<Response2>The god of responsibility does all of your responsibilities for a month! Your followers rejoice at "your" great actions.</Response2>
			<Response3>The god of sharing allows his followers to worship you!</Response3>
		</Events>
	</Goodevents>
</GoodeventsCollection>